I think extracting ourselves from all of
these different conflicts and recognize
that most of them actually don't touch
us and that we should actually learn a
little bit from the Chinese who have
managed to have pretty decent relations
with everyone and despite all of the
different turbulences in the region
managed to stay out of it um and that's
been dramatically successful for them.
It would be for us as well if we just
had the strength to pursue our own
interest unapologetically.
Hi, I'm John Kuryaku and welcome back to
Deep Focus. As we enter the the fall
this year, all eyes are still on the
Middle East and so many people are
predicting yet another Israeli attack on
Iran. Why? Well, we're not really sure.
Is it that the Israelis believe they
haven't finished the job? Is it that
they just want to see some kind of
destruction that's going to result in
the overthrow of the Iranian government?
We're even seeing press reporting here
in the United States quoting the Scoop
Jackson or Henry Jackson Foundation in
London as saying that the Iranian
government is teetering on the brink of
collapse. That's just simply not true.
Those of us who have Iranian friends or
or know people in Iran who are reporting
back saying say that the country lacks
for nothing and it's not teetering on
the brink of anything. Anyway, what
better place to go than to the
acknowledged expert on these issues?
Tria Parsy is an Iranian-born Swedish
writer and activist. He's co-founder and
executive vice president of the Quincsey
Institute for Responsible Statecraft.
That's a place that I rely on. And he's
also founder and former president of the
National Iranianamean Council. Trita,
welcome to the show.
>> Thanks so much for having me. It's great
to be with you.
>> The pleasure is all mine. And I've been
looking forward to this for a long time.
And and I'm going to start right off the
bat. You have an absolutely outstanding
Substack. And I'm not saying that just
because you're on the show. I mean, I've
been reading your Substack since you
started it. And you made a very bold
prediction a couple of months ago. You
said that you thought that the Israelis
were likely to attack Iran again by the
end of August. It looked like they
walked right up to the line and then
they they didn't. Now we're seeing
reporting that well the destruction the
the the damage at the Iranian sites
wasn't as as significant as previously
thought. We're hearing that drum beat
again. And now we're hearing other
analysts say no. Trari may have been
wrong about the timing, but he's right
about the goal and the policy and
another attack is coming. Is that what
we're facing here? Should we expect to
see another Iranian uh sorry, Israeli
attack on Iran?
So what I wrote uh and I think the
substack is referencing the piece I had
in foreign policy. I said that the
window for the attack is most likely
between end of August as the earliest
and sometime in December at its latest.
I put it within that window for a couple
of reasons and and let me first explain
why I think the Israelis are going to do
it again. They had three objectives with
their attack in June. The first one was
partially successful. The other two were
not. The first one was to finally get
the United States into a war with Iran.
This is something the Israelis have
pushed for for more than 20 years. You
know more about it than I do. Finally,
they succeeded. Now, of course, they
wanted the United States to be fully
engaged in the war, take out a lot of
Iran's conventional military
capabilities, but instead Trump just did
a one-off on the nuclear side. So, they
wanted it to continue. Trump did not.
The two other objectives, however, were
not successful. First amongst those was
to make sure that they decapitated the
Iranian regime. They managed to have
some significant intelligence successes.
In the beginning, they assassinated a
large number of Iranian military
officials uh and their families,
including nuclear scientists who are
completely civilian and their families.
But within 12 to 18 hours, the Iranians
had replaced them and then went on the
offensive and started shooting ballistic
missiles at Israel, which over the
course of those 12 days became
increasingly effective in penetrating
Israel's air defense systems. The third
objective is the most important one, and
it's the longer one, and that is to
reduce Iran into another Syria or
Lebanon, a country that Israel can
attack at will with impunity. And most
importantly, without American
involvement, clearly that is not where
Israel is with Iraq right now. Israel
couldn't have done any of this without
massive American involvement, whether
that was on the offensive side that
Trump provided or on the defensive side,
which both Trump and Bided provided in
terms of trying to shoot down the Iraqi
missiles. Now, I do think that the
Israelis expect that they would have
made more advances towards that goal. I
don't think they thought that this is
going to be a one-off and they're going
to be able to reduce Iran into Syria
with one attack, but I do think that
they had expected to go much further.
And I think also they were taken by
surprise by how effective Iran's
missiles were and their capability or
continue to shoot at Israel despite the
many losses the Iranian.
But having started this campaign, the
Israelis cannot afford to stop it from
their standpoint because the more time
is given, the Iranians will be able to
rebuild their air defense system,
perhaps buy better ones from the
Chinese. They will be able to root out
the Mossad presence inside of um uh uh
Iran. They uh the Israelis may lose the
political window that exists with Trump
uh greenlighting these things. So
there's a lot of factors that are
uncertain. Um and and as a result um uh
and also one other important factor
there is the Iranians can build
ballistic missiles faster than the US
and Israel can build missile
interceptors. And they were already
running out of the A3 towards the end of
the 12 days. And we also now know that
the United States spent 25%
of its stockpile of THAAD interceptors
during those 12 days and it will take
the United States 3 to 5 years to
replenish. That was actually what I
wanted to ask you about. I apologize for
interrupting, but we saw a lot of
reports uh as the hostilities were
taking place that Israeli stores were
spent and that the United States had
provided Israel with everything it was
able to provide. We we also heard that
the Israelis were surprised at how the
Iron Dome didn't hold the way it was
always
said that it was able to. that even the
slow motion drones in the in the first
go uh this the first back and forth
between the Iranians and the Israelis uh
saw Iranian drones penetrate the Iron
Dome. Not a lot of them, but it showed
that the Iron Dome wasn't all it was
cracked up to be. So, here we are months
later. We know that the Iranians have
good relations, healthy relations with
with China, with India, with Russia and
other countries. Presumably then they'll
be able to replenish their supplies of
whether defensive or offensive uh
systems
and then what uh and and I'm going to I
want to ask a a sort sort of an addition
to that if if you don't mind addressing
it as well. There is a rumor, a rumor
that Donald Trump didn't really want to
attack Iran, but that Benjamin Netanyahu
said, "If you don't do it, we're going
to use nuclear weapons and that Trump
did it to keep the nuclear aspect out of
this." Can you can you give us your
ideas on on how much of this is true? Do
the Israelis really have the wherewithal
to keep this up? And do you think the
United States thought that maybe it was
doing Iran some sort of a favor by
keeping nuclear weapons out of this?
>> So lot of questions here. So let me try
them one one by one. Um um let me go
first back and point out because it's
related to what you just asked about.
The Israelis were taken aback uh already
back in October of 2024 when they saw
that many of the Iranian missiles
actually did penetrate their many layers
of air defense system. It's not just the
Iron Dome, it's David Slaying, it's the
Patriots, it's um Arrow 1, two, and
three. And then of course as a result of
all of their failures, they asked the
United States to provide the that um and
uh the US did under Biden and they have
kept it there. Uh and it's important to
recognize the US has very limited amount
of those and I think two out of 10 are
now in Israel.
>> Yes.
>> So I mean the amount of support the US
had to give to Israel to be able to do
this and it wasn't even successful
should tell us something about this
narrative that is being pushed by some
in Washington that Israel is now the
US's new as are the region's new
hedgeimon. Certainly I think military
hegemony is something that the Israelis
are pursuing. It is part of their
military doctrine, but it is really not
hegemony if someone else is paying for
it. It is really not hegemony if someone
else has to step in massively in order
for Israel to be able to conduct this
warfare. So rather than actually being a
um a propellant or an amplifier of
American power in the region, in my
view, the Israelis are consuming
American power in the region with very
little return for the United States. Um,
now on to your specific questions.
Precisely because this penetration
occurred, I think Trump only doing a
one-off is a key reason as to why it
only ended up becoming a 12-year war. I
think the Israelis would have been happy
to continue the war as long as the US
was in it. They were taking hits. They
would take even more hits because the
interceptors were running out. But it
was worth the price if the US was in
there because with the US's firepowers
obviously vast superior to what the
Israelis could do. But since Trump only
did a one-off, the ceasefire was
something that the Israelis also saw as
beneficial to them precisely because
they were taking such hits. But this is
also precisely the reason why they will
attack again. Israel does not tolerate
that there are countries in the region
that actually can deter Israel and that
can attack Israel and afflict the cost.
So it's intolerable according to their
military doctrine as a result it needs
to be eliminated. Uh and the longer they
wait the higher the likelihood that many
of these different factors from Iran's
military readiness to uh political
windows closing in Washington uh will
create a much more complicated
situation. So, I put the most likely uh
further end to this somewhere in
December because after that, the US will
enter the midterm election season. We've
already seen that this was not popular
with MAGA. The only reason that it
didn't cost Trump that much is because
it was a one-off from their standpoint
and you know, his him blasting that this
was a major success and it wasn't a long
war. No Americans were killed. the next
war will likely not be like this and as
a result it's not I'm not saying that
the Israeli wouldn't be able to do it in
January or February it's just it will be
much much more complicated of a
political calculation so the most likely
window in my view ends sometime in in
December now going back to the issue of
nukes I'm not sure I have not heard that
rumor I think perhaps that rumor is
seeking to reflect um um uh another
notion which is that in Trump's view in
the view of the White House. They did
this partially because Trump initially
saw this as a success and then wanted to
take credit for it which we clearly saw
but also uh because of the fact that uh
this was seen as a political compromise
between the varying uh waring factions
within the White House. those much
closer to the Israelis, the neocons that
are unfortunately still there who wanted
to have a full-scale uh military
confrontation who of course had the
support of the Israelis and the more
restrained minded people who were
thinking this is just a huge
distraction. We were supposed to get out
of the Middle East. Why are we back in
the Middle East for a war with no clear
and achievable military objectives? We
have spent 25% of our T that
interceptors in a region that both
Biden, Obama, and Trump said is no
longer strategically vital to the United
States. Why are we doing this? The the
compromise in between was a one-off that
would end the war because once Trump had
done this, he put pressure on the
Israelis and we saw how angry he was at
the Israelis.
>> Drop the F.
>> Drop the F. I think it's historically
unprecedented to do so in front of
camera. Um, so it was a way to end it. I
personally think that nevertheless,
if you really didn't want to deal with
this mess, you shouldn't have supported
in the first place.
>> The United States is fully capable of
telling the Israelis, you can't do this
for a very simple reason. We're not
going to defend you. We're not going to
shoot down the missiles you completely
on your own. And imagine how many hits
the Israelis would have taken if the
United States didn't have the fads
there. Didn't use all of it intelligence
capabilities and all other capabilities
to shoot down or identify the missiles
and provide the Israelis with the
intelligence. Israelis would simply not
been able to stand the chance and as a
result the US has massive leverage. The
question is why are we not using it for
our own purposes and our own interests?
I want to ask you as a as a foreign
policy analyst and observer
what does the United States get out of
this? And the reason I ask is that it's
common knowledge that Benjamin Netanyahu
over the last 20 or 25 years, every
single time he came to Washington, he
would ask whoever happened to be
president, help us attack Iran. Every
single time. And every president said no
until Donald Trump said yes. So if the
end result here is going to be what
everybody thinks it's going to be and
that is that the Iranians leave the NPT
and no one could blame them uh and then
come to a policy decision which I think
they probably have already come to that
they have to build a nuclear uh weapon
in order to protect themselves from
another nuclear state.
Then what's what's the win for the
United States? Why carry out a policy
like this in the first place? There is
absolutely none in my view. Our interest
in the region is very very limited. I'm
not one of those China hawks that says
that China is the you know we have to go
to war with China. But clearly East
Asia, many other areas are far more
strategically vital to the United States
than the region is. Everything we do
should be fuel feeding into a larger
effort of reducing America's military
presence in the region. we have still
more than 50,000 troops about 19 bases
in the region. Uh it is not sustaining
stability. In fact, if you compare uh
the situation in 1998 to 2020, there
were about five armed conflicts in the
region in 1998. By 2020, there were
about 22. That is all happening under
the era of American military hijgemony
in the east. And of course many of those
conflicts are a direct result of the
invasion of Iraq which is entirely our
fault. Uh whereas you know I'm not
saying the US is responsible for
everything but that that is coming out
of the Iraq war is on us. Uh there is no
way around that. So I don't think we
have been able to stabilize the region.
Um we've not been um uh and it's not
been serving our interest either. In
fact, we've seen a flourishing of intra
regional diplomacy once regional powers
that are close to us realize that the US
is no longer going to defend them. Once
Trump did not go to war with Iran after
the Iranians attacked Saudi Arabia over
these oil disputes and the matter in
which the Saudis were helping Trump uh
try to eliminate all of Iran's Iran oil
exports, Trump decided not to go to war
with uh Iran back in 2019 that when that
happened. Uh and then later on under
Biden when the Houthis attacked UAE the
Amiradis expected that uh the US would
enter into the war and instead Biden
only issued two two press releases that
send shock waves through the region
making a lot of these countries who have
had a very reckless and aggressive
foreign policy enabled by their belief
correct up to a point that we would back
them up and bail them out in whatever u
uh disasters they would get themselves
into. Once they realized that they
couldn't hide behind American military
power, the prediction of Washington was,
oh, if the US is not there to uphold
stability, we will see deterioration,
instability, all of these different
things. Instead, the exact opposite
happened. These countries started to
invest much more in diplomacy, resolving
their problems with Iran. I'm not saying
that they're in love with Iran in any
way, shape, or form, but diplomacy
suddenly became much more optimal and
and attractive once you no longer could
hide behind American military power,
which then means our military presence
and hegemony in the region has actually
been an impediment to regional diplomacy
for regional states to resolve their own
uh problems by themselves and then as a
result take the burden of security or
fantasy of security off of America's
shoulders. So I think everything we
should do in the region should go
towards trying to help build some sort
of a security architecture in the region
that enables the United States to lead
and recognize that we don't have a dog
in most of these different fights. Who
in Washington I think Marjorie Taylor
Green who has um u emerged as a quite a
strong voice on these matters actually
put it very well in one of her historic
tweets a couple weeks ago and says no
one in my district has ever met a hooti.
They don't even know what a hooti is.
say that. Yes.
>> Yeah. So, so this idea that the Houthis
are a major threat to the United States
from Obama to Biden to Trump and now
back to Trump is is really ridiculous.
We don't have a dog in that fight. In
fact, to the extent that originally uh
we may have had one is completely false
because the Houthis were the main force
against al-Qaeda, which actually we do
have a beef with uh who did kill
Americans in on American soil. So, um I
think extracting ourselves from all of
these different complaintings and
recognize that most of them actually
don't touch us and that we should
actually learn a little bit from the
Chinese who have managed to have pretty
decent relations with everyone and
despite all of the different turbulences
in the region managed to stay out of it.
Um and that's been dramatically
successful for them. It would be for us
as well if we just had the strength to
pursue our own interest
unapologetically.
>> Trita, let's talk about the Chinese for
a minute and the Russians. We can add
the Russians in there as well. Iran has
increasingly close relations with both
of those countries as well as with other
major uh countries, for example, the
BRICS countries, which include Iran and
Brazil and China and India and now a
half dozen other places.
What does this improvement in both
diplomatic and trade relations mean for
Iran? Is it going to be that much harder
for the Israelis and the Americans to
wage war against Iran when they have to
think or consider potential responses
from the Chinese or the Russians.
So we have seen in the last five or
seven years that Iran has managed to
break out of a political isolation that
it's faced. It joined the Shanghai uh
organization. It joined the bricks
mindful of the fact that Iran was not
part of any such regional bodies or
global bodies before. That is a huge
step for the Iranians.
>> But so far it's only had a political
dimension.
>> Economically I don't think we're seeing
a significant increase in trade between
Iran and many countries within the
bricks
>> because they're still afraid of American
sanctions outside of India indirectly
Russia and China. Iran is still
suffering tremendously from the fear
that other countries have from trading
with Iran because of extr territorial
American sanctions. So economically it
definitely sets the stage for a
different uh situation for Iran. It is
still not yet materialized. The same is
also true militarily. We have to
remember BRICS is not a military
organization. It doesn't have a military
dimension. It is not a military pact in
any way, shape or form. It is very
explicitly not such a military pack.
Shanghai conference has more of a
security dimension to it of course but
is also not a military pack. The
Iranians do have a new agreement with
the Russians but that does not amount to
a pact in which they're coming to each
other's defenses. I would say that by
and large the Iranians are quite
disappointed that they had hoped that at
least from Russia they would have gotten
more support mindful of the fact that
the Iranians did provide a tremendous
amount of support to the Russians in
Ukraine. I think their expectations on
the Chinese is far less because everyone
knows the Chinese are clever and
disciplined enough not to get themselves
dragged into other countries conflicts.
But the Iranians have invested heavily
just in the last couple of months. Uh
and we saw that the Iranian foreign
minister said after this meeting in um
Beijing just a couple of days ago that
the meeting that the Iranian president
had with she was one of the most
historically important in Iran's
history. It's difficult to know exactly
what it means, but it seems to be a
pretty big deal. Now, let's say that the
Iranians actually are getting Isra
Chinese uh air defense systems and
fighters. That would nevertheless not
have much of an impact uh for the next
couple of months. That will take years
to implement, train, all of these
different things, which goes back to
what I said earlier on. The window for
the Israelis to attack um is still open
from their standpoint up until sometimes
in December. After that, it gets much
much more complicated.
and uh both politically and militarily
and this is why I think more and more
people are coming to the conclusion that
there might be an attack. Well, let me
throw out one other thing. Uh I'm not
predicting that it will exactly happen
then at all but I would say that perhaps
the likelihood of it happening towards
the end of September at the end of uh
the high level week at the UN General
Assembly in New York because two things
happen. On the one hand, you have the
end of the snapback 30-day negotiation
period. The Europeans have triggered
snapback sanctions on Iran. Those will
come into effect by I think September
26th unless there is some sort of a deal
between the Iranians and the Europeans.
And it doesn't seem very likely because
frankly the Europeans don't seem to be
actually looking for the escalation. I
think they want escalation at this
point. I can go into greater detail as
to why I think that is the case. that
then provides a political window for the
Israelis. Not one that they necessarily
need, but definitely is a political
lubricant because we're talking about a
chapter 7 resolution being reimposed on
Iran for at the UN. Secondly, during
that same week, the French and the
Saudis are making a major push for a
large number of countries to recognize a
Palestinian state. That includes the UK,
it includes Australia, Malta, and a
growing number of European countries.
were the ones who haven't recognized
Palestine yet. So the snapback may
provide a political lubricant. The
Palestine week may provide the reason as
to why Netanyahu will need a
distraction. Those things coming
together may increase the risk of an
attack happening around that time. It
doesn't mean that it will, but if I were
to make it better, I would say it's
probably more likely then than it is 2
weeks later or two weeks before. May I
ask you about the Europeans's uh
snapback uh decision? A lot of people
thought that they would want to
offer up a temporary solution, somehow
postpone the decision because of their
continued adherence to the JCPOA that
there was this weird situation that all
of us in the Western world were in where
we had come to this agreement with the
Iranians that was the JCPOA. the
Americans unilaterally withdrew. The
Europeans remained in it and it allowed
them to do at least some form of trade
with Iran. That appears now to not be
the case. It appears that the Europeans
are moving again to the side of the
Americans. Can you explain that decision
and what it means for
short-term
relations between Western Europe and
Iran?
>> Yeah, I think the geopolitical situation
has changed quite dramatically. It seems
to have in the last 20 years or so from
the European perspective, but also
Europe itself has really changed to the
worst in my view. Uh particularly since
the Russian invasion, but it started a
little bit earlier than that. Um I think
it's important to remember that this
whole constellation of the E3 uh
Germany, UK and France is something that
was invented in 2002 2003. It was not a
constellation that had been given a
mandate by the other European states to
speak for Europe on foreign policy. But
it was an initiative that was taken at
the time because the Iraq war was so
clearly a disaster and the Europeans
were very worried that after Iraq, the
United States would invade Iran as well,
which frankly was in the cards. And they
decided to intervene diplomatically in
order to prevent war. That was the
objective at the time. They managed to
convince the Ivanians to suspend
enrichment
um and as a result dramatically take
away a pretext that the Bush
administration could have used in order
to launch another war in the Middle
East. Now fast forward to 2025, a lot
has changed. I don't think the Europeans
any longer are on this issue working for
deescalation.
they have seen a dramatic change in
their uh security environment and one
thing that is of particular importance
to them is that the Iranians have
supported Russia in Ukraine which means
that the Europeans who in the past did
not see Iran as a threat. They saw the
nuclear program as a challenge but the
real threat was war with Iran. That was
the danger and they tried to prevent
that together with preventing a
potential uh dash for a bomb in Thran.
Now they see Iran actually as a threat
because of its support for Russia which
they define as an existential threat. We
can have a conversation as to whether
that is accurate or not but nevertheless
that's how they are presenting. So the
need to punish Iran I think is something
that was not present in the past in the
calculation or at least not as prevalent
as it was then. But then there's the
other fact which is that the Europeans
really know that they made themselves a
vessel of the United States over the
course of the last couple years. They
had the option of going for strategic
autonomy which I think actually would
have been better for the US as well to
have a more balanced and positive
relationship with Europe rather than
having them become some sort of an
annex. Um but they didn't and instead
after 2022 they double down on being
dependent on the United States. And then
Trump comes in, which they of course
should have been able to predict that at
least there was a high likelihood that
that would happen. And now there is a
disaster in the transatlantic
relationship within the Trump
administration. There is a faction,
however, that is sympathetic to the
Europeans on Ukraine that has tended to
be very hawkish on Russia, Rubio and
many others there. Uh and they have
another priority which is that they
really want to please the Israelis and
they really want to go at Iran very
strong. So I think you see suddenly uh a
trade-off in which the Europeans are
going along with the Rubio faction and
escalation with Iran uh which is you
know again what Ruben wants in return
for hoping I don't think there's a
promise but for hoping that that will
lead to a scenario in which Trump will
become more amenable to Europe's
perspective on Russia and uh Ukraine
which for the Europeans is far more
important than Iran. We have to remember
that over the course of the last 20
years of all these different sanctions,
there is no trade between Iran and
Europe, there was a moment in which 20%
of Spain's um oil came from Iran. A very
large portion of Greece and and Italies
as well. That is no longer the case
since 2012 or so in which the Europeans
completely wean themselves off of Iran.
So there is no economic implications any
longer um uh for constant escalation
with Iran. Iran has also been weakened
in the region. So I think the Europeans
are less worried about it. But they're
very angry about the Iranian support for
Ukraine and they're very worried about
Russia and this is a trade-off that from
the European perspective makes sense.
And you know we can debate that but I
think it's important to understand where
this is coming from and then at a
minimum recognize do not give the
Europeans the benefit of the doubt of
thinking that everything they're doing
with Iran is in the direction of
deescalation. It no longer is.
>> It's not. One last question and I know
that you're pressed for time and I I
promise to let you go. I spent years
living in Bahrain, Kuwait, Saudi Arabia.
Back then, and I'm talking about the the
1990s into the early 2000s, there was a
deep and abiding hatred of Iran and and
distrust of Iran. Um, at least
diplomatically, that seems to be changed
or in the process of changing. Do you
believe this is a temporary situation or
have we entered a new period of
diplomatic relations between the the
Gulf countries and Iran?
>> I think we have entered a new diplomatic
era. Um it is no by no ch by no ways um
something that cannot be changed back to
something much more negative. And again,
I think the key factor is that once
these countries realize, ooh, we can't
hide behind American power. Pushing the
US to take military action against Iran
is no longer an option. And even if it
happened, now we also know that Iran
actually can uh damage these countries
tremendously because it takes far I
think it takes about 7 minutes for an
Iranian missile to hit Abu Dhabi. It
takes 12 to 18 minutes to reach um um u
Israel. Uh, and these are shorter range
missiles that are um that the Iranians
have far greater amounts of, right? I
may have gotten some of these numbers uh
wrong, but the the portion I think is
correct. The point being that they
recognize Iran actually can be very
painful to them. They can hide behind
American power. There is a willingness
in Tean for diplomatic reconciliation
and it actually makes sense for everyone
else in the region as well. So, I hope
that it's long-standing because from an
American perspective, it is actually
better for us. let these guys get along,
have stability, make sure that it we
don't have all of these different uh
pushes for the US to get involved in
their quarrels or in their fights. Um uh
let trade and other things work out.
That is much better for us than to think
that we have to be military present,
that we have to have uh military
hegemony in the region or the fear that
the Iranians will have military
hygemony. The Iranians clearly are not
in a position to be able to establish
hegemony in the region. they've already
lost uh tremendously but even if before
that they didn't have that capability in
fact there is no country in the region
including Turkey that has the capability
of establishing hegemony and the extra
regional powers Russia and China are not
dumb enough to try to seek hegemony in
the Middle East because what's the
benefit of it there is no benefit treats
such a great treat uh to have you thank
you so much for this conversation and uh
we would love to do it again I
appreciate for joining us.
>> Well, treat Oh, no. Fantastic. Before
you go, real quickly, where can people
read more of uh of your work? You're at
the Quincy Institute for Responsible
Trade Craft. You have an incredible
Substack. Is that the best place for
people to go?
>> Yes, they can go to the Substack. I
think it's just parcy
institute is quincy nst.org.
>> Fantastic. Thanks for joining us.
>> Thanks so much.